# **YANIV WEINSHTEIN**

Full-Stack Developer

Email Address Phone Number GitHub Profile Portfolio LinkedIn Profile yanivwein22@gmail.com 0544718317 YanivWein24 Yaniv-Weinshtein Yaniv-Weinshtein

## **Summary**

Full-stack developer specializing in the MERN stack. With a practical engineering degree in electronics, and a great passion for technology and innovation. Enjoys building web applications, with a tendency towards the front-end, and finding new documentations to explore!

#### **Experienced with the following libraries and technologies:**

Front-End: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Next.js, Redux, Context, React-Query, Axios,

Formik, Styled components, Material-UI, Bootstrap, SCSS, CSS, HTML

Back-End: Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Prisma, Socket-IO, JWT, Passport.js, Oauth2.0

Misc: Jest, Es-Lint, Git, Linux, Circle-CI, Postman, Python

## **Work experience**

#### Jan 2023 - Present: Socialo | Full Stack Developer | Freelance

React, Node.js, MongoDB, Oauth, TypeScript, Context, React-Query, Formik, Styled-Components, Material-UI

Developing an AI-based SAAS digital marketing platform for businesses and marketing agencies. Integrating with Open-AI and the top social networks to automate the process of creating, refining, and publishing professional content on social media. Enabling companies to efficiently create and maintain high-quality content quickly and with ease.

## Oct 2022 - Feb 2023: eBigay | Front-End Developer | Volunteering

React, TypeScript, PWA, Context, React-Query, Formik, Styled-Components, Material-UI

Working in the frontend team for a marketplace web app that connects donors with those in need. Developing responsive and user-friendly UI from scratch, according to the given design in Figma. Consuming the server API and collaborating with the back-end team. Working with SCRUM methodology.

## **Projects**

#### **Similarity API**

#### Next.js, TypeScript, Next-Auth, Prisma, Open-AI, Redis, TailwindCSS, Radix-UI

A Full-Stack Next.js project, containing a rate-limited API in the back-end and a user dashboard with documentation in the front-end. The API receives 2 pieces of text, converts them to vectors, and returns a number between 0-1 representing the similarity of the 2 vectors.

- Project
- GitHub Repository

#### Get Jokes

#### React, Redux, Bootstrap, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Passport, Oauth2.0

A MERN Stack web app that fetches jokes from a variety of over 1000 jokes, according to the user's queries. Users can create free accounts and save the jokes they liked in a personal collection.

Includes unit tests and CI/CD, and a custom dark mode that applies automatically on dark-themed devices

- Project
- GitHub Repository

## **Education And Courses**

- Javascript Algorithms And Data Structures Masterclass by Colt Steel , Udemy | 2022
- The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp by Dr. Angela Yu, Udemy | 2022
- Practical Engineering In Electronics | Kziney Yam Acre | 2017-2019

## **Military Experience**

## July 2019 - March 2022: Power And Control Systems Technician | Israeli Navy

Locating and solving complex problems in large-scale systems.

Ensuring the power and control systems are working properly and the navy ships are qualified to go on to their missions.